Why'd you switch sides?
(Sheldon:)Be grateful
I'm still in the room.
(Amy:)Comfy?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm just happy
I don't know
(Sheldon:)what this memory
foam remembers.
(Amy:)Sheldon?
(Amy:)I know we took coitus
off the table,
(Amy:)but I was wondering how you feel
about other forms of intimacy,
(Amy:)such as snuggling.
(Sheldon:)Well, it's funny
you should ask,
(Sheldon:)because I was wondering
how you'd feel
(Sheldon:)about separating the two
of us with a pillow wall.
(Amy:)Sheldon, I've made more than
enough accommodations for you.
(Amy:)We're both grown adults--
(Amy:)we've been far more
intimate than this.
(Raj:)If you don't want
to snuggle, fine--
(Amy:)but we're not building
a pillow wall.
(Sheldon:)Okay, well, I am sorry.
(Sheldon:)I'm just worried that my
sensitivity to temperature
(Sheldon:)could make this
a rough night.
And no offense, but your
bottom radiates enough heat,
(Sheldon:)I'm surprised there aren't
iguanas lying on it.